Guide to the George Champion Papers, 1925-2019, MS 3241
New-York Historical Society
- Speeches, 1966-1971 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 11)
  • A Changing World's Challenge to Business (Third Annual Conference, International Iron and Steel Institute, Tokyo, Japan, Oct. 13, 1969).
  • Remarks (Manufacturing Chemists Association, New York City, Nov. 24, 1970).
  • New Dimensions in Urban Action (New York Chamber of Commerce monthly meeting, June 3, 1971).
- Speeches, 1973-1975 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 12)
  • City of Opportunity (Semi-Annual Meeting, National Board of Directors, Boys Clubs of America, University Club of New York, Dec. 3, 1973).
  • Museum of the City of Opportunity (Second Draft [crossed out], Nov. 12, 1974).
  • Museum of the City of Opportunity (Museum of the City of New York, Annual $24 Award" Dinner, Nov. 25, 1974).
  • In Unity There is Action (Bronx Chamber of Commerce, Inc., 81st Annual Meeting and Luncheon, Dec. 5, 1974).
  • Remarks (The Hundred Year Association of New York, Inc. 43rd Annual Dinner, draft of Sep. 8, 1975).
  • Help Wanted: Effective Management for New York City (The Hundred Year Association of New York, Inc. 43rd Annual Dinner, New York, Oct. 1, 1975).
  • The Forgotten Majority (1975?).
- Speeches, 1976-1986, undated (Offsite-box 3, Folder 13)
  • New York City Management and Financial Situation (New York Chapter, American Statistical Association, April 19, 1976).
  • Untitled speech to Arthur Andersen group, Oct. 1976 (first outline draft, Sep. 8, 1976).
  • Management Volunteer Plan (draft, Sep. 14, 1976).
  • Untitled draft (1976?).
  • "Operation Grassroots." New York: Yesterday…Today…Tomorrow (March 16, 1977).
  • Comments of George Champion, Chairman, Economic Development Council, for Public Hearings on the Board of Education (May 24, 1977).
  • Remarks (11th Annual Meeting, Economic Development Council, May 24, 1977).
  • 1978: Year of Opportunity For Business Management in City Government (Semi-Annual Meeting, Economic Development Council, Nov. 21, 1977).
  • Statement for Press Conference at Chamber of Commerce and Industry (March 21, 1978).
  • Remarks (Annual Meeting, Economic Development Council, May 24, 1979).
  • Testimony (Senate Banking Committee, Feb. 15, 1983).
  • Address (Annual Summer Meeting Committee for Monetary Research & Education, Inc., New York City, July 16, 1986) [3 copies; copy 1 with emendations; copy 2 with attached list of attendees?; + correspondence with CMRE President Elizabeth B. Currier].
  • A Positive Program For Commercial Banks (undated).
  • Untitled draft of speech to Arthur Anderson & Co. (undated).
  • Untitled draft (undated).
- Strategic Plan—Financial Services Industry, circa 1984 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 14)
  Draft of "Strategic Plan. The Federal Role in Preserving the Integrity of Financial Services and Markets."
- Trips—Brazil, 1963 March 13-26 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 15)
  "Clippings of publicity in Rio de Janeiro and São Paulo papers until March 21, 1963."
- Trips—Europe, 1952 April-September (Offsite-box 3, Folder 16)
  Itineraries, correspondence, and receipts documenting Champion's trip to Europe, June 11-July 15, 1952, with stops in London, Copenhagen, Frankfurt, Baden-Baden, Zurich, Rome, and Paris. Printed lists of passengers for voyages on the R.M.S. Queen Mary (June 11) and S.S. United States (July 10) are found in Box 1, Folder 21.